Guide to Illinois Institute of Technology Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00098
Cubberley Education Library
Illinois Institute of Technology (formed by the merger of Armour Institute of Technology and Lewis Institute)
1895-1974
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00098
155 item(s)
Located in Chicago, Illinois. Formed by the merger of Armour Institute of Technology (founded 1892) and Lewis Institute (founded 1894) in 1940. In 1940 included: Armour College of Engineering (formerly Armour Institute), Lewis Institute of Arts and Sciences (formerly Lewis Institute), Graduate School (founded in 1937) and Armour Research Foundation (founded in 1936. Merged with Chicago-Kent College of Law in 1969. Chicago-Kent College of Law was formed by the merger of Chicago College of Law (founded in 1887) and Kent College of Law (founded in 1892). Founded Stuart Graduate School of Business in 1969.
Illinois; Technical colleges; Law schools
- Armour Institute of Technology, 1895-1941; 50 item(s) Yearbooks [catalogs] for 1895/96-1906/07 Bulletins for 1907-1914, 1918-1937, 1939-1940/41
  - American School of Correspondence, 1904-1905; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1904 & 1905.
  - Armour Institute of Technology President's Report, 1933-1939; 6 item(s) Reports for 1933/34, 1935-1939
- Chicago College of Law, 1898-1899; 1 item(s) Catalog of 1898/99
- Chicago-Kent College of Law, 1900-1970; 48 item(s) Announcements for 1900/01, 1910/11-1914/15, 1921/22, 1924/25-1926/27, 1928/29-1930/31, 1934/35-1960/61, 1962/63-1969/70
- Illinois Institute of Technology, 1941-1974; 55 item(s) Announcements for 1944/45, 1946/47-1947/48 Bulletins for 1961/64-1972/74 Catalog supplement for 1961/63
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Armour College of Engineering, 1941-1942; 1 item(s) Announcements 1941/42
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Lewis Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1941-1943; 2 item(s) Announcements for 1941/42-1942/43
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Graduate School, 1942-1977; 11 item(s) Announcements for 1942/43-1943/44, 1946/47-1954/56, 1960, 1976/77
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Undergraduate Catalog, 1948-1961; 7 item(s) Catalogs for 1948/49, 1950-1951, 1953, 1957/58, 1959/61
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Institute of Gas Technology, 1949-1950; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1949/50 Brochure on Institute of Gas Technology Fellowships [no date]
  - Illinois Institute of Technology President's Report, 1950-1964; 10 item(s) Reports for 1950/51, 1952/53, 1954/55-1955/56, 1957/58-1960/61, 1962/63-1963/64
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Industrial Engineering, 1957; 1 item(s) Booklet prepared by the IIT Student Chapter of the American Institute of Industrial Engineers.
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Chicago-Kent College of Law, 3 item(s) Bulletins for 1970/71-1971/73, 1975/76
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Institute of Design, 1957-1960?; 2 item(s) Brochures for 1957, [1960?]
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Summer Session, 1965-1966; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1965 & 1966.